Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco Papers
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1905-1968 (Box 1-106)
  - Works with opus number, 1910-1968
    - Op. 59: Crinoline (piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Op. 60: 3 Heine Lieder, II Heft (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 118
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Op. 60: 3 Heine Lieder, III Heft (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 119 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Op. 61: Ouverture per la bisbetica domata
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Op. 61: Ouverture per la bisbetica domata (piano, 4 hands or 2 pianos)
      - Manuscript score (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Op. 62: 6 odi di Orazio (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 68
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Op. 63: Fantasia e fuga sul nome di Ildebrando Pizzetti (piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Op. 64: The lark (violin, piano)
      - Printed score, see also Jascha Heifetz Collection, ML31.H4a (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Op. 65: Media difficoltà (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 76
      - Printed score (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Op. 65: Ritmo di tango (violin, piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Op. 66: I profeti (violin, orchestra)
      - Printed full score, see also Jascha Heifetz Collection, ML31.H4a (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 64/3)
      - Printed piano-violin score (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Op. 67: 2 film studies (piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Op. 68: Ballade des biens immeubles (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Op. 69: Quintetto in fa (piano, string quartet)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 7
      - Printed score (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Parts (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Op. 70: 2o trio in sol (violin, violoncello, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 51
      - Printed score (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Parts (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Op. 71: Variazioni attraverso i secoli (guitar)
      - Manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 66
      - Printed score (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Op. 72: Concerto (violoncello, orchestra)
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Printed piano-violoncello score (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Violoncello part (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Op. 73: Ouverture per La dodicesima notte
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Op. 74: 2 sonetti del Petrarca (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Op. 74: Petrarca-Chopin: 3 madrigali (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Op. 75: Dos romances viejos (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 94
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Op. 75: La ermita di San Simon (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 69
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Op. 75: La ermita di San Simon (voice, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Op. 75: Romances viejos, II series (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Op. 75: Romance del Conde Arnaldos (voice, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Op. 76: Ouverture per Il mercante di Venezia
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Op. 77: Sonata: omaggio a Boccherini (guitar)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Op. 78: Ouverture al Giulio Cesare
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Op. 79: Trois poèmes de la Pléïade (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Op. 80: Ouverture per Il racconto d'inverno
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 6
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Op. 81: Savonarola (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 8
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Op. 81: Savonarola. Lauda di Nostra Donna (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 138
    - Op. 81: Savonarola. Lauda di Nostra Donna (voice, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 16/2)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 16/3)
      - Parts (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Op. 81: Savonarola. Lo the Messiah (women's voices, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Op. 81: Savonarola. Lo the Messiah (voices, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Op. 81: Savonarola. Lo the Messiah (men's chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 16/6)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Op. 81: Savonarola. Mary, star of the sea (women's chorus, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Op. 81: Savonarola. Mary, star of the sea (chorus, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Op. 82: Notturno sull'acqua (violoncello, piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 16/9)
      - Violoncello part (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Op. 82: Scherzino (violoncello, piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 16/10)
      - Violoncello part (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Op. 83: Toccata (violoncello, piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Violoncello part (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Op. 84: Tre preludi alpestri (piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Op. 85: Cappricio diabolico (guitar)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Op. 85: Cappricio diabolico (guitar, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 104
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Manuscript full score (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Op. 87: Tarantella (guitar)
      - Manuscript score (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Op. 87: Aranci in Fiore (guitar)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Op. 88: Trois fragments de Marcel Proust (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Op.89: Louisiana (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 123 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Op. 89: Leaves of grass (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Op. 89: Ocean (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 17/11)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Op. 90: Lecho dodi (cantor, men's chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Op. 90: Lecho dodi (cantor, chorus, organ)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 47
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Laid in: Clara Castelnuovo-Tedesco manuscript notes; [1] p. (Box-folder 64/4)
      - 2 photocopied manuscript piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 64/4)
      - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Photocopied printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Op. 91: Féeries (voice, piano)
      - 2 holograph manuscript piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Op. 91: Charmes
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 18/4)
      - 2 manuscript piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Op. 92: 2° concerto in fa (piano, orchestra
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see also ML96.C34 no. 14 (Box-folder 18/5-7)
      - Holograph manuscript score for 2 pianos, see ML96.C34 no. 15
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score for 2 pianos (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Op. 93: Concertino (harp, string quartet, clarinets)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 13
      - Manuscript score (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Op. 93: Concertino (harp, chamber orchestra)
      - Parts (Box-folder 19/2-6)
      - Holograph / copyist manuscript piano-harp score (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Op. 94: I giganti della montagna (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 5
      - Parts (Box 20-22)
    - Op. 94: I giganti della montagna (orchestra; 1938 version)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 64/5)
      - Manuscript short score (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Saxophone part (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Op. 95: J’ai du bon tabac: variations plaisantes (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 73
      - Manuscript score (Box-folder 23/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Op. 96: Goccius (voices)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 107
    - Op. 97: 3 Shakespeare duets (voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 23/3)
      - 2 manuscript piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Op. 97: 3 Shakespeare duets (voices, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Op. 98: Aucassin et Nicolette (voice, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see also ML96.C34 no. 1 (Box-folder 65/1-4)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score, see also ML96.C34 no. 1 (Box-folder 65/5-8)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score, see also ML96.C34 no. 1 (Box 66)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 24/3)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 25/2-5)
      - Parts (Box-folder 26/1-2)
    - Op. 98: Aucassin et Nicolette (voice(s), orchestra; 1964 version)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score, Acts II-IV only; Act III has altered portions for soprano and baritone (Box 26/3)
    - Op. 99: Concerto in D major (guitar, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 3
      - Photocopied manuscript full score (Box-folder 27/1)
      - Manuscript piano-guitar score (Box-folder 27/2)
      - Printed piano-guitar score (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Op. 100: Scottish songs (voices, harp, strings)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Op. 100: Scottish songs (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 125
      - Printed piano-vocal score, All songs present except Hunting song and Proud Maisie (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Op. 100: Scottish songs. Jock of Hazeldean (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 140
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Op. 101: Un sonetto di Dante (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 144 (Box-folder 27/7)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Op. 102: Concerto no. 3 (violin, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-violin score (Box-folder 27/8)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Op. 103: Pansies (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Op. 104: Stars (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Op. 105: Recuerdo (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 133
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Op. 106: The legend of Jonas Bronk (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 121
      - Printed piano-vocal score, Laid in: holograph manuscript libretto; [2] p. (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Op. 106: New York (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 126
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Op. 107: Ballade (violin, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 27/14)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Op. 108: Overture to A midsummer night's dream
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 67/1)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Op. 109: Upon his blindness (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score, Published title: When I consider how my life is spent (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Op. 110: La figlia del reggimento (violin, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 28/2)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 28/2)
      - Printed score of "Valse" (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Op. 111: Overture to King John
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Op. 112: Larchmont Woods (violin, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 28/4)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Op. 113: Keats songs (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Op. 113: Keats songs. Homer (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 120
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/5)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Op. 113: Keats songs. The mermaid tavern (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Op. 113: Keats songs. Homer (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 75
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Op. 113: Keats songs. The mermaid tavern (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Op. 113: Keats songs. Psyche (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 75
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/9)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Op. 113: Keats songs. On the grasshopper and the cricket (women's chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 75
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Op. 114: London (Upon Westminster Bridge) (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 147
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 28/11)
    - Op. 115: The birthday of the infanta (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 53
      - Holograph manuscript short score, Laid in: typescript program notes; [2] p. (Box-folder 29/1)
      - Photocopied manuscript short score, Includes annotations and cuts for concert performance (Box-folder 29/2)
      - Parts (Box-folder 29/3-10)
      - Parts (Box 30-31)
    - Op. 116: Indian songs and dances (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 77
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 67/4)
      - Photocopied manuscript short score (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Op. 117: Le rossignol (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 137
    - Op. 117: Le rossignol (women's voices, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Op. 118: Serenade (guitar, orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 32/3)
      - Guitar part, see ML96.C34 no. 161
      - Printed piano-guitar score (Box-folder 32/4)
      - Guitar part (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Op. 119: Divertimento (2 flutes)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 16
      - Printed score (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Op. 120: The princess and the pea (orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 67/5)
      - Parts (Box 33)
    - Op. 121: Five humoresques on themes of Foster (orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 67/6)
      - Parts (Box-folder 34-35)
    - Op. 122: Sacred service for Sabbath eve (cantor, chorus, organ)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 36/1)
      - Cantor part (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Op. 122: Sacred service for Sabbath eve. May the words (voice, piano)
      - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Op. 122: Sacred service for Sabbath eve. 5 preludes (organ)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 72
      - Printed score (Box-folder 36/2)
    - Op. 122: Sacred service for Sabbath eve. Addenda (chorus, organ)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Contents: Lecho dodi, Kiddush, Ma tovu, Hashkivenu (Box-folder 36/3)
      - Manuscript vocal score, Rendition of Sacred Service with addenda (Box-folder 36/3)
      - Photocopied manuscript vocal score, Rendition of Sacred Service with addenda. Kiddush and Tov l'hodos not used; Laid in: translations of texts and list of durations; [6] p. (Box-folder 36/3)
    - Op. 122: Sacred service for Sabbath eve. Silent devotion (string orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 36/4)
    - Op. 123: Candide (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 10
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 36/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 36/5)
    - Op. 123: Candide (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, Unfinished (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Op. 124: Ozymandias (voice, piano)
      - 3 holograph manuscript piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Op. 124: The daffodils (voice, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Op. 124: The shadow (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 142
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 36/8)
    - Op.125: Shakespeare sonnets (voice(s), chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Sonnet no. 154 is a cappella (Box-folder 37/1)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Sonnet no. 154 is a cappella (Box-folder 37/2)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Addenda, composed 1963 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Op. 126: Aubade (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 100
    - Op. 126: Carol for Candlemas Day (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 105
    - Op. 126: To His Son (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 146
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Op. 127: Sonata (violin, viola)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 29
      - Parts (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Op. 128: Sonata (clarinet, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 173
      - Clarinet part, see ML96.C34 no. 173
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 37/6)
      - Clarinet part (Box-folder 37/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 37/7)
      - Clarinet part (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Op. 129: Rondo (guitar)
      - Printed score, see also Moldenhauer Archives, ML31.M6 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Op. 130: Sonatina (bassoon or violoncello, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 174
      - Bassoon and violoncello parts, see ML96.C34 no. 174
      - Printed score (Box-folder 38/1)
      - Bassoon and violoncello parts (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Op. 131: 5 poesie romanesche (voice, piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 38/2)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Op. 132: Venice (men's chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score, see ML96.C34 no. 148
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Op. 133: Suite (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 32 and Ml96.C34 no. 158
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 38/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Op. 134: Overture to Anthony and Cleopatra
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 68/2)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 68/3)
      - Parts (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Op. 135: Overture to The tragedy of Coriolanus
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 68/4)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 68/5)
      - Parts (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Op. 136: The octoroon ball (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 52
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 68/7)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 38/6-7)
    - Op. 137: Naomi and Ruth (women's voices, piano or organ)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 38/8)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 38/8)
      - Photocopied manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Op. 137: Naomi and Ruth. Aria of Ruth (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 124
    - Op. 137: Naomi and Ruth. Aria of Ruth (voice, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 38/9)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 68/8)
    - Op. 137: Naomi and Ruth. Aria of Naomi (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 38/10)
    - Op. 138: Suite nello stile italiano (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 31
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 38/11)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Op. 139: Second string quartet
      - Holograph manuscript score, see also ML96.C34 no. 25 (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Op. 140: The book of Ruth (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box 69)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Op. 141: Evangelion (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 98
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 70/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Op. 142: Six canons (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 11
      - Printed score (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Op. 143: Guitar quintet (guitar, string quartet)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 26
      - Manuscript short score (Box-folder 40/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 40/2-3)
    - Op. 144: Sonata in C minor (viola, violoncello)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 30
      - Printed score (Box-folder 40/4)
      - Parts (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Op. 145: Fantasia (guitar, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 19
    - Op. 146: Concerto de camera (oboe, string orchestra, optional horns and timpani)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 70/2)
    - Op. 146: Concerto de camera. Aria (oboe, violoncello, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 40/5)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Op. 146: Concerto de camera. Aria (oboe, violoncello, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Op. 147: Third string trio (violin, viola, violoncello)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 40/8)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 40/9)
      - Parts (Box-folder 40/8-9)
    - Op. 148: Sonata (violin, violoncello)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 41/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Op. 149: 2 songs by Longfellow. The day is done (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 83
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Op. 149: 2 songs by Longfellow. Nature (chorus)